=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 22=
= الحلقة 22 =
Weiyi, are you hungry?
ويي ، هل أنت جائع؟
No.
رقم.
Shall I send you home?
هل سأعيدك للمنزل؟
No, thanks.
لا شكرا.
I like to take the bus.
أحب ركوب الحافلة.
I'll keep you company then.
سأحافظ على صحبتك بعد ذلك.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
He gave up just like that?
استسلم تماما مثل هذا؟
(Please forgive me)
(رجائاً أعطني)
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
are you out of your mind?
هل جننت؟
Don't you think it's embarrassing?
ألا تعتقد أنه محرج؟
Weiyi, have you forgiven me?
وييي ، هل سامحتني؟
Let's have luosifen together.
دعونا نتناول luosifen معًا.
Weiyi, I know beautiful girls like luosifen,
ويي ، أعرف فتيات جميلات مثل لوسيفين ،
but I didn't expect you to like it too.
لكنني لم أتوقع أن تعجبك أيضًا.
If you love me, you have to eat it together with me.
إذا كنت تحبني ، عليك أن تأكله معي.
I'll do it!
سأفعل ذلك!
Mr. Bai,
السيد باي ،
my ideal home
بيتي المثالي
has to have the smell of luosifen.
يجب أن يكون لها رائحة لوسيفين.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
You have great taste.
لديك ذوق رائع.
I love it.
أنا أحبه.
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
I know you provided for my father
أعلم أنك قدمت لوالدي
for my sake.
من أجل مصلحتي.
However, you don't understand my family.
ومع ذلك ، أنت لا تفهم عائلتي.
Once you are targeted by him,
بمجرد أن يتم استهدافك من قبله ،
he'll demand money from you constantly.
سيطلب منك المال باستمرار.
If so, I can try to understand your family starting from now.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك ، يمكنني محاولة فهم عائلتك بدءًا من الآن.
Honesty is the most important element
الصدق هو أهم عنصر
in a relationship.
فى علاقة.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
I hope you won't need to worry about anything
أتمنى ألا تقلق بشأن أي شيء
when you're with me.
عندما تكون معي.
How much did you spend on them?
كم أنفقت عليهم؟
Not much. It's quite cheap.
ليس كثيراً.  إنها رخيصة جدًا.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Excuse me. Which of you is Miss Sun Weiyi?
اعذرني.  من منكم الآنسة صن ويي؟
I am.
انا.
This bouquet was sent by Mr. Bai Zeliu.
تم إرسال هذه الباقة من قبل السيد باي زيليو.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
What flowers are these?
ما هذه الزهور؟
They look like cotton flowers.
تبدو مثل أزهار القطن.
His net worth is over 100 million
صافي ثروته أكثر من 100 مليون
yet he's so stingy.
ومع ذلك فهو بخيل جدا.
These aren't ordinary flowers.
هذه ليست زهور عادية.
These are preserved flowers.
هذه زهور محفوظة.
They can maintain this state forever,
يمكنهم الحفاظ على هذه الحالة إلى الأبد ،
which represents eternal bliss.
الذي يمثل النعيم الأبدي.
Miss Sun, Mr. Bai said
قال السيد باي الآنسة صن
that we have to send them to your office every day
أنه يتعين علينا إرسالها إلى مكتبك كل يوم
if you like them.
إذا كنت تحبهم.
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
stop sending me gifts in public
توقف عن إرسال الهدايا لي في الأماكن العامة
in the future.
فى المستقبل.
But why?
لكن لماذا؟
I want everyone to know
اريد ان يعرف الجميع
that you are my girlfriend.
أنك صديقتي.
But
ولكن
Q is a blabbermouth.
Q هو ثرثار.
If she knows,
إذا كانت تعلم ،
the entire company will know about it.
ستعرف الشركة بأكملها عن ذلك.
They constantly ask me to treat them to meals.
يطلبون مني باستمرار أن أقدم لهم وجبات الطعام.
It's not like your money simply appears in your pocket.
ليس الأمر كما لو أن أموالك تظهر ببساطة في جيبك.
Weiyi, are you concerned about me now?
وييي ، هل أنت قلق علي الآن؟
Judging from your tone,
انطلاقا من نبرة صوتك ،
you'll be a stern wife.
ستكون زوجة صارمة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Once we get married,
بمجرد أن نتزوج ،
you'll be in charge of all my money.
ستكون مسؤولاً عن كل أموالي.
Who are you calling your wife?
بمن تتصل بزوجتك؟
Mrs. Bai.
السيدة باي.
Alright. Alright.
على ما يرام.  على ما يرام.
Who are you calling your wife?
بمن تتصل بزوجتك؟
You're not my wife. You're Mrs. Bai.
أنت لست زوجتي.  أنت السيدة باي.
I'm not either!
انا ايضا لست كذلك!
Hey, daughter of the chairman of the adulterated food company,
يا ابنة رئيس شركة الاغذية المغشوشة ،
are you trying to harm people again?
هل تحاول إيذاء الناس مرة أخرى؟
We had been consuming your products since young!
لقد كنا نستهلك منتجاتك منذ الصغر!
We never expected your father to be such a sly man!
لم نتوقع أبدًا أن يكون والدك رجلًا ماكرًا!
He's inhumane!
إنه غير إنساني!
Do you know
هل تعرف
how many children had consumed your adulterated food products?
كم عدد الأطفال الذين تناولوا منتجاتكم الغذائية المغشوشة؟
Some of them have been suffering from malnutrition,
بعضهم يعاني من سوء التغذية ،
even disabilities!
حتى الإعاقات!
And you?
وأنت؟
You're squandering
أنت تبدد
our hard-earned money
أموالنا التي حصلنا عليها بشق الأنفس
to lead a wealthy life.
ليعيشوا حياة غنية.
You must be enjoying yourself, huh?
لا بد أنك تستمتع بوقتك ، أليس كذلك؟
Exactly!
بالضبط!
Shameless wretch!
بائس وقح!